## JENNY CITHERLET

P: 604 935 6304

E: jennycith@gmail.com

## **SUMMARY**

I am a resourceful CRM Marketing Automation Specialist with experience in project management. I specialize in the template creation, development, deployment, and analytics of email campaigns.

I utilize strong organizational, planning and communication skills towards improving operational efficiency. I worked with Agile methodologies, and I have a passion for people and technology. With a comprehensive background in digital media and web technologies, I am a problem-solver with excellent analytical and negotiation skills. I am committed to providing the best customer experience as well as continuous improvement.

#### **SKILLS**

- 8+ yrs. of experience in HTML emails, landing pages and marketing Automation
- Experience in list segmentation, data privacy and legal compliance for email campaigns
- Strong working knowledge of CMS, HTML, CSS, email client specificities, A/B testing
- Experience using ERPs (Oracle, SAP for HR), Salesforce Marketing Cloud
- Dynamic and reliable team-player with proven organizational and communication skills
- Customer service attitude and trustworthy, positive approach. Experience working remotely
- Create, test and maintain web pages with WP and other CMS
- Project Management Professional (PMP)®

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### **EMAIL DEVELOPER — IMPLEMENTATION SPECIALIST**

APRIL 2023 TO PRESENT

## (FREELANCE)

- Building collateral (HTML transactional email, Marketing campaigns and landing pages) for clients.
- Advocate best practices in email design, content strategy, and digital marketing using CSS to meet design specifications of customers for the specific application.
- Use enterprise-level email service platform to manage email lists, conduct audience segmentation and A/B testing, and deployment.
- Manage projects involving clients and various internal departments.
- Create, test, and maintain web pages with WP and other CMS.

## GUESTFOLIO - CENDYN, WHISTLER, BC

May 2014 - March 2023

## ACCOUNT PRODUCER & CONTENT SPECIALIST (CONTRACTOR & EMPLOYEE)

Guestfolio (Cendyn), an award-winning and trusted guest engagement platform for hospitality data. We work in partnership with hoteliers and provide an integrated single-source solution that manages all day-to-day transactional communications, guest satisfaction and digital marketing programs.

- Responsible for on-boarding and building new accounts. Uses creative and digital skills to build collateral (HTML/CSS automated email marketing solution, newsletter, Mobile Concierge app & survey) for our hotel clients worldwide.
- Improved email content and design to improve open & click rate by +34%. Improved list segmentation and increased property revenue.

# MIKE WIEGELE HELICOPTER SKIING, BLUE RIVER, BC LEAD SKI GUIDE

NOVEMBER 2006 - PRESENT (PART-TIME & FULL-TIME)

• Provide international guests with one of the best ski experiences on the planet while managing risk in an uncontrolled mountain environment.

# WHISTLER HELI-SKIING, WHISTLER, B.C., CANADA GROUND OFFICE MANAGER & ADMINISTRATOR

DECEMBER 2004 – FEBRUARY 2014

- Managed and trained team of 15 Sales Associates
- Monitored and tracked accounts payable/receivable
- Acted as the main contact for booking agents and provided booking agents with Product Knowledge Sessions
- Built and maintained strong business partnerships to deliver a high level of service
- Created and implemented tools & processes for tracking reservations and seat bookings
- Coordinated administration & communication on a daily basis

#### ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- Experience working with Agile methodologies
- Project Management Professional (PMP)®
- Proficient in Adobe Creative Suite, Microsoft Office, Google Docs, Asana, Slack, Teams, Figma
- Experience using ERPs (Oracle, SAP)
- Instructional Skill Workshop
- Fluent in French/English

### **EDUCATION**

0	Project Management PMP®	Project Management Institute	2023
0	,	Lighthouse Labs, Vancouver, BC	2020
0	Digital Marketing & Social Media	British Columbia Institute of Technology	2019
0	Web Technologies	British Columbia Institute of Technology	2013
0	Business Diploma	Ecole Supérieure de Commerce, Switzerland	2002